A Guide to the League of Women Voters of the Richmond Area Archives 1920-1997
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Donations made after 2003, 1979-1991 (Box 13)
  - General Election, 1988 (Box-folder 13:12)
  - General Election, 1985 (Box-folder 13:13)
  - Handbook for Local League Ladies, 1979 (Box-folder 13:14)
  - League of Women Voters Annual Report, 1983 (Box-folder 13:15)
  - Making a Difference, 1978 (Box-folder 13:16)
  - Miscellaneous Voters Service, late 1970s to early 1980s (Box-folder 13:17)
  - Newspaper, the Gazette, 1984 (Box-folder 13:18)
  - Non-Partisan Voter's Guide, 1989 (Box-folder 13:19)
  - Old Clippings, 1979 (Box-folder 13:20)
  - Open Door Policy for Voting Rights, 1981 (Box-folder 13:21)
  - Outreach, Registration, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 13:22)
  - PAC s Local, 1987 (Box-folder 13:23)
  - Presidential Debates, General, 1988 (Box-folder 13:24)
  - Questionnaire, 1987 (Box-folder 13:25)
  - Recycling, 1988 (Box-folder 13:26)
  - Registration Information, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 13:27)
  - Registration Project, 1984 (Box-folder 13:28)
  - Richmond City Council Questionnaire, 1988 (Box-folder 13:29)
  - Samples of Other US Leagues, 1970s (Box-folder 13:30)
  - Special Elections, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 13:31)
  - Super Tuesday, 1988 March 8 (Box-folder 13:32)
  - US Annual Reports, 1979 (Box-folder 13:33)
  - Voter Guide, 1988 (Box-folder 13:34)
  - Voter Guide, 1989 (Box-folder 13:35)
  - Voter s Guide Candidate Questionnaire, 1989 (Box-folder 13:36)
  - Voter s Guide Examples, Includes Richmond and Other LWV Chapters, 1991 (Box-folder 13:37)
  - Voter s Guide Project--Candidate Responses, 1991 (Box-folder 13:38)
  - Voter Registration Practices in Virginia, 1984 (Box-folder 13:39)
  - Voter Registration Project--MX 106--Radio, 1988 (Box-folder 13:40)
  - Voter Service, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 13:41)
  - Voter Service, 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 13:42)
  - Voter Service--Questionnaires and Pamphlets, 1986 (Box-folder 13:43)
  - WWBT-TV 12--Voter Service, 1988 (Box-folder 13:44)
- Donation Made in 2006 1977-2006 (Box 13a-19)
  - 75th Anniversary Convention, 1995 (Box-folder 13a:1)
  - Adult Domestic Violence Fundraiser, 1993 (Box-folder 13a:2)
  - America Votes PSA, 1992 (Box-folder 13a:3)
  - Annual Meetings, 1983, 1993, 1994, 2000, 2005,2006 (Box-folder 13a:4)
  - Annual Reports, 1997-2005 (Box-folder 13a:5)
  - Board of Directors, circa 1990s (Box-folder 13a:6)
  - Board Meetings, 1979, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 13a:7)
  - Board Meetings, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 13a:8)
  - Board Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 13a:9)
  - Board Meetings, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 13a:10)
  - Board Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 13a:11)
  - Board Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 13a:12)
  - Board Meetings, 1995 (Box-folder 13a:13)
  - Board Meetings, 1996 (Box-folder 13a:14)
  - Board Meetings, 1997 (Box-folder 13a:15)
  - Board Meetings, 1998 (Box-folder 13a:16)
  - Board Meetings, 1999 (Box-folder 14:1)
  - Board Meetings, 2000 (Box-folder 14:2)
  - Board Meetings, 2001 (Box-folder 14:3-5)
  - Board Meetings, 2002 (Box-folder 14:6-7)
  - Board Meetings, 2003 (Box-folder 14:8)
  - Board Meetings, 2004 (Box-folder 14:9-10)
  - Board Meetings, 2005 (Box-folder 14:11)
  - Board Meetings, 2006 (Box-folder 14:12)
  - Board Members and Information, undated (Box-folder 14:13)
  - Bylaws, undated (Box-folder 14:14)
  - Bylaws and Policies, undated (Box-folder 14:15)
  - Call 12 Voter Registration Watch Program, 1995 October 17 (Box-folder 14:16)
  - Campaign Watch, 1992 (Box-folder 14:17)
  - Candidate Questions, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 14:18)
  - Candidate Questionnaire, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 14:19)
  - Child Care, circa 1994 (Box-folder 14:20)
  - Children at Risk and Juvenile Justice, 1990s (Box-folder 14:21)
  - Children First in Virginia, 1990s (Box-folder 14:22)
  - City Celebrations, 1999-2003 (Box-folder 14:23)
  - City Council and School Board Elections, 1996 (Box-folder 14:24)
  - Congressional Questions, 1996 (Box-folder 14:25)
  - Contact Lists, undated (Box-folder 14:26)
  - Correspondence and Notes, circa 1990s (Box-folder 14:27)
  - Decision 1992, 1992 (Box-folder 14:28)
  - Directories, 1990s (Box-folder 14:29)
  - Directories and Reference Books, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 14:30)
  - Education Committee Reports, 1991-2003 (Box-folder 15:1)
  - Education, Family Life 1963-1979, 1987 (Box-folder 15:2)
  - Facts for Voters, 1984-1996 (Box-folder 15:3)
  - Facts for Voters, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 15:4)
  - Fair Housing, 1973-1989 (Box-folder 15:5)
  - Fiscal Policy Committee, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 15:6)
  - Forum, Candidate, 1994, 1998-1999, 2003 (Box-folder 15:7)
  - Forum, Mayoral, 2002-2004, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 15:8)
  - Forum, Patriot Act, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 15:9)
  - Fundraising, 1992-1995, 1999 (Box-folder 15:10)
  - General Assembly, 2001 (Box-folder 15:11)
  - Get Out the Vote Grant, 2000 (Box-folder 15:12)
  - Government, Local Study, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 15:13-14)
  - Henrico County PTA, 2007 (Box-folder 15:15)
  - Holiday Parties, 1996-2004 (Box-folder 15:16)
  - Holiday Spoofs, 1997, 1998, 2000 (Box-folder 15:17)
  - House of Delegates, 2001 (Box-folder 15:18)
  - Impact on Issues, 1986-1988, 1998-200 (Box-folder 15:19)
  - Improving Legislative Process, 1999 (Box-folder 15:20)
  - In League Guidelines for League Boards, 1984 (Box-folder 15:21)
  - International Republican Institute, 2000 (Box-folder 15:22)
  - Juvenile Justice Study, 1996 (Box-folder 15:23)
  - League Catalogues, 1993, 1995, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 15:24)
  - League Conventions, 1993-1999, 2001 (Box-folder 15:25)
  - League Day, 1983, 1997, 2000, 2001, 2003, 2005 (Box-folder 15:26)
  - League Number, VA105 Information, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 15:27)
  - League President s Packet--Platforms, Organization, Bylaws, 1984, 1989, 1992, undated (Box-folder 15:28)
  - League of Women Voters of the United States, undated (Box-folder 16:1)
  - The Leaguer, 1977 June-1878 October (Box-folder 16:2)
  - The Leaguer, 1978 November-1982 September (Box-folder 16:3)
  - The Leaguer, 1984 May-1986 March (Box-folder 16:4)
  - The Leaguer, 1986 April-1987 September (Box-folder 16:5)
  - The Leaguer, 1987 October-1988 May (Box-folder 16:6)
  - The Leaguer, 1988 June-1989 February (Box-folder 16:7)
  - The Leaguer, 1989 March-1991 March (Box-folder 16:8)
  - The Leaguer, 1991 April-1992 November (Box-folder 16:9)
  - The Leaguer, 1994 May-1996 November (Box-folder 16:10)
  - The Leaguer, 1996 December-1998 November (Box-folder 16:11)
  - The Leaguer, 1999 January-2001 May (Box-folder 16:12)
  - The Leaguer, 2001 September-2003 October (Box-folder 17:1)
  - The Leaguer, 2003 November-2005 April (Box-folder 17-2)
  - Maggie Walker Students win We the People Competition, circa 2000 (Box-folder 17:3)
  - Mailing Lists, undated (Box-folder 17:4)
  - Mayor-at-Large Debate, circa 2003 (Box-folder 17:5)
  - Meet the Candidate Chesterfield, 1999 (Box-folder 17:6)
  - Meet the Candidates Nights, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 17:7)
  - Membership and Contacts, 1997-2003 (Box-folder 17:8)
  - Membership Directory, 1993-2006 (Box-folder 17:9)
  - Member s Handbook, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 17:9)
  - Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box-folder 17:10)
  - 1988 August-1994 June and July (Box-folder 17:11)
  - National Voter, 1994 September-October-1997 June-July (Box-folder 17:12)
  - National Voter, 1997 September-October-2008 February (Box-folder 17:13)
  - Official Statements on Local Matters, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 17:14)
  - Pamphlets, Programs, Flyers, late 1980s-early 2000s (Box-folder 17:15)
  - Photographs-Annual Meetings, 1999 (Box-folder 17:16)
  - Photographs-Annual Meetings, 2000 (Box-folder 17:17)
  - Photographs-Annual Meetings, 2001 (Box-folder 17:18)
  - Photoraphs-Black History Tour, 2001 (Box-folder 17:19)
  - Photographs-Campaign Finance Reform Town Meeting, 2000 (Box-folder 17:20)
  - Photograph-Convention, 1999 (Box-folder 17:21)
  - Photographs: Field Trip to Montepeleir for We the People Competition, circa 1999 (Box-folder 18:1)
  - Photographs: Friday Cheers, circa 2000 (Box-folder 18:2)
  - Photographs: League Day, 1999 (Box-folder 18:3)
  - Photographs: League Day-Juvenile Justice, 1999 (Box-folder 18:4)
  - Photographs: LWVVA Convention, 2001 (Box-folder 18:5)
  - Photographs: LWVRMA at the National Convention, 2000 (Box-folder 18:6)
  - Photographs: Meet the Candidates, 1999 (Box-folder 18:7)
  - Photographs: Meet the Candidates Chesterfield, 1999 (Box-folder 18:8)
  - Photographs: Meet the Candidates Henrico, 1999 (Box-folder 18:9)
  - Photographs: Meet the Candidates and Membership Tea, 1999 (Box-folder 18:10)
  - Photographs: Negatives, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 18:11)
  - Photographs: River City Beer and Seafood Festival, circa 2000 (Box-folder 18:12)
  - Photographs: U.S. Department of State Meetings of NGOs, Washington D.C., circa 2000 (Box-folder 18:13)
  - Photographs: Virginia Voter Registration Workshop, circa 2000 (Box-folder 18:14)
  - Photographs: Voter Service-Youth Leadership Forum, 2001 August (Box-folder 18:15)
  - Photographs: Wednesdays on the Waterfront, circa 2000 (Box-folder 18:16)
  - Policy and Guidelines, Bylaws, 1977, 1984, 1988, 1992-1995, 1997 (Box-folder 18:17)
  - Positions in Brief 1990s (Box-folder 18:18)
  - Positioned for Action, 1998 (Box-folder 18:19)
  - Presidential Debates, 1998 (Box-folder 18:20)
  - Program Health Care, 2000 (Box-folder 18:20)
  - Program Planning, Late 1980s to Early 2000s (Box-folder 18:21)
  - Program Planning Report, 2003 (Box-folder 18:22)
  - Project Vote Smart, 1994 (Box-folder 18:23)
  - Publication, 1990s to early 2000s (Box-folder 18:24)
  - Publication Kit, undated (Box-folder 18:25)
  - Recycling Project, undated (Box-folder 18:26)
  - Report of the State of Council, 1994 (Box-folder 18:27)
  - Restorative Justice, circa 1997 (Box-folder 18:28)
  - Richmond Counts Project, 1999 (Box-folder 18:29)
  - Richmond Transit Study, 1998 (Box-folder 18:30)
  - Special Events, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 18:31)
  - State of the Metro Area Dinner, 1994 (Box-folder 18:32)
  - State Voter Guide, 1994 (Box-folder 18:33)
  - The Status of Women in Virginia, 1996 (Box-folder 18:34)
  - Strategic Planning, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 18:35)
  - Take Back the System, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 18:36)
  - Transportation Initiatives for Greater Richmond, 2003 (Box-folder 18:37)
  - U.S. Department of State Provided Materials, 2002 November (Box-folder 18:38)
  - The Virginia Voter, 1995 August-1999 Spring (Box-folder 18:39)
  - The Virginia Voter, 1999 Fall-2004 Spring (Box-folder 18:40)
  - Vision 20-10, 2000 September 20 (Box-folder 18:41)
  - Voter Guides, mid 1980s to early 2000s (Box-folder 18:42)
  - Voter Guide Richmond 7th District, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 18:43)
  - Voter Redistricting, 2008 (Box-folder 18:44)
  - Voter Registration, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 18:45)
  - Voter Service, 1980s-2007 (Box-folder 18:46-47)
  - Voter Service Registration, 2000-2008 (Box-folder 18:48)
  - Water Conservation, with Correspondence from Lillian Throckmorton, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 18:49)
  - Water Study Committee, 1977-1982, 2000 (Box-folder 18:50)
  - Women's Round Table, 1998 January 22, 1998 January 28 (Box-folder 18:51)
  - Oversize News Clippings, Posters and Certificates, 1992-2004 (Box-folder 19:1)
- Donations made in 2013, 2003-2012 (Box 20)
  - Annual Reports, 2003-2012 (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Records of the Boards, 2007 June 30-2009 April 27 (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Records of the Boards, 2009 April 27-2012 June 19 (Box-folder 20:3)